aspfree.com 2007-06-24

# Developer Shed - Privacy Policy

**DEVELOPER SHED INC. PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Developer Shed, LLC ("DEVELOPER SHED, LLC"), comprised of the Internet sites Developer Shed, LLC, developershed.com, devshed.com, aspfree.com, devarticles.com, scripts.com, devhardware.com, devarchives.com, seochat.com, devmechanic.com, and webhosters.com (the "DEVELOPER SHED, LLC Sites"), is committed to protecting the privacy of users of the DEVELOPER SHED, LLC Sites. At DEVELOPER SHED, LLC, we do our best to provide as much security as possible concerning personal information and registration data. As part of the normal operation of the DEVELOPER SHED, LLC Sites, we collect information from you. This Privacy Statement describes the information we collect and how that information may be used. 

**INFORMATION GATHERED THROUGH THE DEVELOPER SHED, LLC SITES:**

DEVELOPER SHED, LLC will track the domains from which people visit the DEVELOPER SHED, LLC Sites in order to gain aggregate data that may be analyzed for trends and statistics. Subject to the provisions of this Privacy Statement, DEVELOPER SHED, LLC may use accumulated aggregate data for several purposes including, but not limited to, marketing analysis, evaluation of DEVELOPER SHED, LLC's services, and business planning. 

Currently, DEVELOPER SHED, LLC uses personal information as a basis for notifications to users, and in order to implement the Terms and Conditions of Use governing the DEVELOPER SHED, LLC Sites (the "Terms"). Generally, the user names, email addresses, and any additional information that a user may choose to post are publicly available on the DEVELOPER SHED, LLC Sites. When users voluntarily and publicly disclose personal information that may contain Registration Data, as defined in the Terms, or otherwise post personal information in conjunction with content subject to a license, such personal information necessarily will be disclosed subject to the terms of the applicable license. An example of such a disclosure includes, but is not limited to, a user's disclosure of personal information as part of a message posted to a public message forum. 

DEVELOPER SHED, LLC may conduct surveys or other studies of its user base and usage for marketing and planning purposes. Participation in such surveys is at the user's option. With respect to information collected from such surveys or studies, and in the event that responses are to be publicly disclosed, users will be notified at the time they take the survey and DEVELOPER SHED, LLC will disclose only aggregate information regarding its users and not personal information identifying any specific individual. Circumstances under which DEVELOPER SHED, LLC would publicly disclose aggregate information include, but are not limited to, sharing survey results with the site population, providing data to DEVELOPER SHED, LLC advertisers on user preferences and/or demographics, business planning, and publicizing overall usage data in press communications. 

**Cookies:** DEVELOPER SHED, LLC employs "cookies" to provide users with tailored information. A "cookie" is an element of data that a website, when visited by a user, sends to that user's browser which, in turn, may store that element on the user's hard drive or memory. DEVELOPER SHED, LLC uses cookies to better serve users of our DEVELOPER SHED, LLC Sites; any cookies sent by DEVELOPER SHED, LLC will be marked so that they will be accessible only by DEVELOPER SHED, LLC Sites subject to this Privacy Statement. However, at his or her option and at his or her sole expense and responsibility, any user may block or delete our cookies from his or her hard drive. However, by disabling cookies, certain site features and functionality may no longer work properly, or at all. 

**Other Notification:** In order to implement or enforce the Terms, DEVELOPER SHED, LLC may use user-provided e-mail addresses to contact users on an individual basis. At no time, unless such disclosure is required by law, a governmental agency, or specifically authorized by the user, will DEVELOPER SHED, LLC disclose individual user personal information to unrelated third parties that is not publicly available. 

**LINKS WITH OTHER SITES**

The DEVELOPER SHED, LLC Sites contain links to other websites, whether owned or controlled by DEVELOPER SHED, LLC affiliates, or unrelated third parties. Please note that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from those of the DEVELOPER SHED, LLC Sites. DEVELOPER SHED, LLC is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any linked website. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of any website you may visit. 

**CHOICE**

"Opt-in" Emails: Users may "opt-in" to receive site notifications, newsletters, or other information via email. Users may remove themselves from such services at their discretion. Any email sent to an "opt-in" list will include directions for how a user may remove himself or herself from the list, or the URL where the user may remove themselves is [ http://www.developershed.com/optout.php](http://www.developershed.com/optout.php). 

Profile Display: In some cases, users' personal information may be publicly available through a user's profile display such as our forums. In such cases, users have the option to opt out of publicly displaying their personal information, including e-mail addresses. Users may also enlist this technique when posing comments on certain DEVELOPER SHED, LLC Sites. In cases where site profiles allow users to display optional information publicly, such entry and display is at the user's discretion and may be changed at any time by the user. 

**SECURITY**

To secure site integrity, DEVELOPER SHED, LLC employs measures, including but not limited to security audits, use of encryption tools and software, and other reasonable security measures and procedures. 

Internal access to users' private and nonpublic personal information is restricted to site administrators and individuals on a need-to-know basis. 

**ENFORCEMENT**

In the event that DEVELOPER SHED, LLC becomes aware that site security is compromised or nonpublic user information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to external security attacks, DEVELOPER SHED, LLC shall take reasonable measures which it deems appropriate, including but not limited to internal investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities, notwithstanding other provisions of this Privacy Statement. 

If DEVELOPER SHED, LLC becomes aware that a user's personal information provided to DEVELOPER SHED, LLC has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this Privacy Statement, DEVELOPER SHED, LLC shall make reasonable efforts to notify the affected user, as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law, of what information has been disclosed, to the extent that DEVELOPER SHED, LLC knows this information. 

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**

We use several third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp. ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

**UPDATES TO THE PRIVACY STATEMENT**

To update the Privacy Statement, we will post both the changed version and its effective date at [http://www.DeveloperShed.com/privacy.php. ](http://www.developershed.com/privacy.php)

**NO GUARANTEES FOR FACTORS BEYOND DEVELOPER SHED, LLC's CONTROL**

While this Privacy Statement expresses DEVELOPER SHED, LLC's standards for maintenance of private data, it is not in a position to guarantee that the standards will always be met. There may be factors beyond DEVELOPER SHED, LLC's control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, DEVELOPER SHED, LLC disclaims any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of private information. 

Last modified: 12/14/04

|
